[
    {
        "input_text": "My name is John Reyes and I live in West Amanda. You can reach me at ronniepennington@example.org.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 21,
                "text": "John Reyes"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 36,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "West Amanda"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 97,
                "text": "ronniepennington@example.org"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 97,
                "text": "ronniepennington@example.org"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 21,
                "text": "John Reyes"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 36,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "West Amanda"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 86,
                "end": 97,
                "text": "example.org"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 198.236.186.2 was accessed by James Miller.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "James Miller"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "198.236.186.2"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "198.236.186.2"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "James Miller"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "198.236.186.2"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Driver license 610 MMF belongs to Henry Cox who resides in New Rebekah.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 43,
                "text": "Henry Cox"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 59,
                "end": 70,
                "text": "New Rebekah"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "610 MMF"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 43,
                "text": "Henry Cox"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 59,
                "end": 70,
                "text": "New Rebekah"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Kendra Smith's SSN is 587-83-0107 and works in Port Christophertown.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "text": "Kendra Smith"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 47,
                "end": 67,
                "text": "Port Christophertown"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 22,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "587-83-0107"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 14,
                "text": "Kendra Smith's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 22,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "587-83-0107"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 47,
                "end": 67,
                "text": "Port Christophertown"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Elizabeth Berry booked flight tickets on 2014-05-01 and paid using card 560578314034.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "text": "Elizabeth Berry"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 41,
                "end": 51,
                "text": "2014-05-01"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 72,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "560578314034"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "text": "Elizabeth Berry"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 41,
                "end": 51,
                "text": "2014-05-01"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_BANK_NUMBER",
                "start": 72,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "560578314034"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 72,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "560578314034"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Please contact Morgan Hayes on 001-207-845-4838x05014 regarding the issue.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 27,
                "text": "Morgan Hayes"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 31,
                "end": 53,
                "text": "001-207-845-4838x05014"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 27,
                "text": "Morgan Hayes"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 31,
                "end": 53,
                "text": "001-207-845-4838x05014"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Visit http://gonzalez-soto.com/ for more information or email martinezkelly@example.org.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 62,
                "end": 87,
                "text": "martinezkelly@example.org"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "http://gonzalez-soto.com/"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 62,
                "end": 87,
                "text": "martinezkelly@example.org"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "http://gonzalez-soto.com/"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "http://gonzalez-soto.com/"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 76,
                "end": 87,
                "text": "example.org"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "John Sheppard booked flight tickets on 1993-03-21 and paid using card 6540945293581690.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "text": "John Sheppard"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 39,
                "end": 49,
                "text": "1993-03-21"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 70,
                "end": 86,
                "text": "6540945293581690"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 70,
                "end": 86,
                "text": "6540945293581690"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "text": "John Sheppard"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 39,
                "end": 49,
                "text": "1993-03-21"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_BANK_NUMBER",
                "start": 70,
                "end": 86,
                "text": "6540945293581690"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 70,
                "end": 86,
                "text": "6540945293581690"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 44.136.18.175 was accessed by Rachel Russo.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "Rachel Russo"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "44.136.18.175"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "44.136.18.175"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "Rachel Russo"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "44.136.18.175"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Passport number P61095989 is registered under Andrew Schwartz.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "Andrew Schwartz"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P61095989"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "Andrew Schwartz"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P61095989"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P61095989"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Stephanie Greene booked flight tickets on 2003-08-11 and paid using card 3578722484370429.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "text": "Stephanie Greene"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 42,
                "end": 52,
                "text": "2003-08-11"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 89,
                "text": "3578722484370429"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 89,
                "text": "3578722484370429"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "text": "Stephanie Greene"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 42,
                "end": 52,
                "text": "2003-08-11"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_BANK_NUMBER",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 89,
                "text": "3578722484370429"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 89,
                "text": "3578722484370429"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Passport number P80622978 is registered under Dr. Gabriel Rich.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 62,
                "text": "Dr. Gabriel Rich"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P80622978"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 62,
                "text": "Gabriel Rich"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P80622978"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P80622978"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 1
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Passport number P33587484 is registered under Jennifer Patel.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 60,
                "text": "Jennifer Patel"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P33587484"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 60,
                "text": "Jennifer Patel"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P33587484"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P33587484"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 19.250.51.180 was accessed by Beth Fleming.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "Beth Fleming"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "19.250.51.180"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "19.250.51.180"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "19.250.51.180"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "Beth Fleming"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "19.250.51.180"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Please contact David White on 797-928-3651x097 regarding the issue.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 26,
                "text": "David White"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 30,
                "end": 46,
                "text": "797-928-3651x097"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 26,
                "text": "David White"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 30,
                "end": 46,
                "text": "797-928-3651x097"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Driver license V50-ASG belongs to Shannon Gibson who resides in South Jordan.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 48,
                "text": "Shannon Gibson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 64,
                "end": 76,
                "text": "South Jordan"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "V50-ASG"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 48,
                "text": "Shannon Gibson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 64,
                "end": 76,
                "text": "South Jordan"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 18,
                "text": "V50"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Emily Chapman's SSN is 651-21-8745 and works in South Eric.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "text": "Emily Chapman"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 48,
                "end": 58,
                "text": "South Eric"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 23,
                "end": 34,
                "text": "651-21-8745"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "text": "Emily Chapman's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 23,
                "end": 34,
                "text": "651-21-8745"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 48,
                "end": 58,
                "text": "South Eric"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Alexis Byrd and I live in Lake Seanberg. You can reach me at edward63@example.com.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "Alexis Byrd"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 50,
                "text": "Lake Seanberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 72,
                "end": 92,
                "text": "edward63@example.com"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 72,
                "end": 92,
                "text": "edward63@example.com"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "Alexis Byrd"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 50,
                "text": "Lake Seanberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 81,
                "end": 92,
                "text": "example.com"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Visit http://johnson.info/ for more information or email leslienelson@example.com.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 57,
                "end": 81,
                "text": "leslienelson@example.com"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 26,
                "text": "http://johnson.info/"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 57,
                "end": 81,
                "text": "leslienelson@example.com"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 26,
                "text": "http://johnson.info/"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 70,
                "end": 81,
                "text": "example.com"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Visit http://beck.biz/ for more information or email fraziershane@example.net.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 53,
                "end": 77,
                "text": "fraziershane@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "http://beck.biz/"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 53,
                "end": 77,
                "text": "fraziershane@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 20,
                "text": "http://beck.bi"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 66,
                "end": 77,
                "text": "example.net"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 1
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Driver license L12 1HY belongs to Douglas Anderson who resides in South Courtney.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 50,
                "text": "Douglas Anderson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 66,
                "end": 80,
                "text": "South Courtney"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "L12 1HY"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 50,
                "text": "Douglas Anderson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 66,
                "end": 80,
                "text": "South Courtney"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 18,
                "text": "L12"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Nicole Esparza and I live in Stanleyberg. You can reach me at albert63@example.net.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "Nicole Esparza"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 40,
                "end": 51,
                "text": "Stanleyberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 93,
                "text": "albert63@example.net"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 93,
                "text": "albert63@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "Nicole Esparza"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 40,
                "end": 51,
                "text": "Stanleyberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 82,
                "end": 93,
                "text": "example.net"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Nicole Woods booked flight tickets on 1975-01-07 and paid using card 3563968035374934.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "text": "Nicole Woods"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 38,
                "end": 48,
                "text": "1975-01-07"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "3563968035374934"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "3563968035374934"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "text": "Nicole Woods"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 38,
                "end": 48,
                "text": "1975-01-07"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_BANK_NUMBER",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "3563968035374934"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "3563968035374934"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Deanna Downs's SSN is 626-13-5513 and works in Michaelberg.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "text": "Deanna Downs"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 47,
                "end": 58,
                "text": "Michaelberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 22,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "626-13-5513"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 14,
                "text": "Deanna Downs's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 22,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "626-13-5513"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 47,
                "end": 58,
                "text": "Michaelberg"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 213.60.129.165 was accessed by Brenda Davis.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 62,
                "text": "Brenda Davis"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "213.60.129.165"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "213.60.129.165"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 62,
                "text": "Brenda Davis"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Aaron Horne and I live in Joechester. You can reach me at campbellchristopher@example.net.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "Aaron Horne"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "Joechester"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 100,
                "text": "campbellchristopher@example.net"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 100,
                "text": "campbellchristopher@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "Aaron Horne"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "Joechester"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 89,
                "end": 100,
                "text": "example.net"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Stephanie Henry booked flight tickets on 2004-04-21 and paid using card 4559160836673.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "text": "Stephanie Henry"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 41,
                "end": 51,
                "text": "2004-04-21"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 72,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "4559160836673"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 72,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "4559160836673"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "text": "Stephanie Henry"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 41,
                "end": 51,
                "text": "2004-04-21"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_BANK_NUMBER",
                "start": 72,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "4559160836673"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 72,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "4559160836673"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 199.57.9.56 was accessed by Alfred Bennett.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 47,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "Alfred Bennett"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "199.57.9.56"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "199.57.9.56"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 47,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "Alfred Bennett"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 11.145.193.213 was accessed by Samuel Harris.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 63,
                "text": "Samuel Harris"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "11.145.193.213"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "11.145.193.213"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 63,
                "text": "Samuel Harris"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Passport number P76975028 is registered under Zachary Walker.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 60,
                "text": "Zachary Walker"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P76975028"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 60,
                "text": "Zachary Walker"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P76975028"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P76975028"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 60.190.65.238 was accessed by Stephanie Rasmussen.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 68,
                "text": "Stephanie Rasmussen"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "60.190.65.238"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "60.190.65.238"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 68,
                "text": "Stephanie Rasmussen"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "60.190.65.238"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Driver license 174LAN belongs to Cody Davis who resides in North Danielle.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 33,
                "end": 43,
                "text": "Cody Davis"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 59,
                "end": 73,
                "text": "North Danielle"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 21,
                "text": "174LAN"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 33,
                "end": 43,
                "text": "Cody Davis"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 59,
                "end": 73,
                "text": "North Danielle"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Allen Garrison's SSN is 484-81-8331 and works in Morganfurt.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 14,
                "text": "Allen Garrison"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 59,
                "text": "Morganfurt"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 24,
                "end": 35,
                "text": "484-81-8331"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "text": "Allen Garrison's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 24,
                "end": 35,
                "text": "484-81-8331"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 1
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Matthew Livingston's SSN is 787-77-7420 and works in South Courtney.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 18,
                "text": "Matthew Livingston"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 53,
                "end": 67,
                "text": "South Courtney"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 28,
                "end": 39,
                "text": "787-77-7420"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 20,
                "text": "Matthew Livingston's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 28,
                "end": 39,
                "text": "787-77-7420"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 53,
                "end": 67,
                "text": "South Courtney"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Derrick Harper's SSN is 625-22-5262 and works in North Samantha.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 14,
                "text": "Derrick Harper"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 63,
                "text": "North Samantha"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 24,
                "end": 35,
                "text": "625-22-5262"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "text": "Derrick Harper's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 24,
                "end": 35,
                "text": "625-22-5262"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 63,
                "text": "North Samantha"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Robert Hall and I live in Darrylstad. You can reach me at john30@example.com.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "Robert Hall"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "Darrylstad"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 87,
                "text": "john30@example.com"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 87,
                "text": "john30@example.com"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "Robert Hall"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "Darrylstad"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 76,
                "end": 87,
                "text": "example.com"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Visit https://www.taylor-rose.org/ for more information or email teresawilliams@example.net.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 65,
                "end": 91,
                "text": "teresawilliams@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 34,
                "text": "https://www.taylor-rose.org/"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 65,
                "end": 91,
                "text": "teresawilliams@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 34,
                "text": "https://www.taylor-rose.org/"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 80,
                "end": 91,
                "text": "example.net"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Driver license F42 8FA belongs to Kara Archer who resides in East Steven.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 45,
                "text": "Kara Archer"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 61,
                "end": 72,
                "text": "East Steven"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "F42 8FA"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 45,
                "text": "Kara Archer"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 61,
                "end": 72,
                "text": "East Steven"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 18,
                "text": "F42"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Please contact Adrian Watts on 001-488-944-0609 regarding the issue.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 27,
                "text": "Adrian Watts"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 31,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "001-488-944-0609"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 27,
                "text": "Adrian Watts"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 1,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 1
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Visit https://zimmerman-smith.biz/ for more information or email jamesanderson@example.net.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 65,
                "end": 90,
                "text": "jamesanderson@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 34,
                "text": "https://zimmerman-smith.biz/"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 65,
                "end": 90,
                "text": "jamesanderson@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 34,
                "text": "https://zimmerman-smith.biz/"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "https://zimmerman-smith.bi"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 79,
                "end": 90,
                "text": "example.net"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 1
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Eric Bentley and I live in New Cynthiamouth. You can reach me at ssmall@example.org.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 23,
                "text": "Eric Bentley"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 38,
                "end": 54,
                "text": "New Cynthiamouth"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 76,
                "end": 94,
                "text": "ssmall@example.org"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 76,
                "end": 94,
                "text": "ssmall@example.org"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 23,
                "text": "Eric Bentley"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 38,
                "end": 54,
                "text": "New Cynthiamouth"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 83,
                "end": 94,
                "text": "example.org"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Please contact Heather Crawford on (772)619-0345x64453 regarding the issue.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "Heather Crawford"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 35,
                "end": 54,
                "text": "(772)619-0345x64453"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "Heather Crawford"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 35,
                "end": 54,
                "text": "(772)619-0345x64453"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Sarah Brown booked flight tickets on 2020-08-05 and paid using card 3514919199063896.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "text": "Sarah Brown"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "2020-08-05"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 68,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "3514919199063896"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 68,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "3514919199063896"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "text": "Sarah Brown"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "2020-08-05"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_BANK_NUMBER",
                "start": 68,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "3514919199063896"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 68,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "3514919199063896"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Passport number P41703447 is registered under Emily Oneill.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 58,
                "text": "Emily Oneill"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P41703447"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 58,
                "text": "Emily Oneill"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P41703447"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P41703447"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Michelle Nguyen and I live in North Rodney. You can reach me at grayjessica@example.net.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 26,
                "text": "Michelle Nguyen"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 41,
                "end": 53,
                "text": "North Rodney"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 75,
                "end": 98,
                "text": "grayjessica@example.net"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 75,
                "end": 98,
                "text": "grayjessica@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 26,
                "text": "Michelle Nguyen"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 41,
                "end": 53,
                "text": "North Rodney"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 87,
                "end": 98,
                "text": "example.net"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 54.16.220.65 was accessed by Sean Garcia.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 48,
                "end": 59,
                "text": "Sean Garcia"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "54.16.220.65"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "54.16.220.65"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 48,
                "end": 59,
                "text": "Sean Garcia"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Robert Hoover's SSN is 475-58-9116 and works in Arellanoport.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "text": "Robert Hoover"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 48,
                "end": 60,
                "text": "Arellanoport"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 23,
                "end": 34,
                "text": "475-58-9116"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "text": "Robert Hoover's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 23,
                "end": 34,
                "text": "475-58-9116"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 48,
                "end": 60,
                "text": "Arellanoport"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Melissa Watson and I live in Michelleberg. You can reach me at devinhodges@example.org.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "Melissa Watson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 40,
                "end": 52,
                "text": "Michelleberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 74,
                "end": 97,
                "text": "devinhodges@example.org"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 74,
                "end": 97,
                "text": "devinhodges@example.org"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "Melissa Watson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 40,
                "end": 52,
                "text": "Michelleberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 86,
                "end": 97,
                "text": "example.org"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Monique Lee and I live in Robertaport. You can reach me at ywatts@example.net.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "Monique Lee"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 48,
                "text": "Robertaport"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 70,
                "end": 88,
                "text": "ywatts@example.net"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 70,
                "end": 88,
                "text": "ywatts@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "Monique Lee"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 48,
                "text": "Robertaport"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 77,
                "end": 88,
                "text": "example.net"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Passport number P86858575 is registered under Richard Zavala.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 60,
                "text": "Richard Zavala"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P86858575"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 60,
                "text": "Richard Zavala"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P86858575"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P86858575"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Melissa Sharp and I live in Longberg. You can reach me at sandra28@example.org.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 24,
                "text": "Melissa Sharp"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 39,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "Longberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 89,
                "text": "sandra28@example.org"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 89,
                "text": "sandra28@example.org"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 24,
                "text": "Melissa Sharp"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 39,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "Longberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 78,
                "end": 89,
                "text": "example.org"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Please contact Angela Mckinney on 001-243-502-9205 regarding the issue.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "Angela Mckinney"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 50,
                "text": "001-243-502-9205"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "Angela Mckinney"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 50,
                "text": "001-243-502-9205"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Please contact Jason Collins on +1-607-527-2095x58489 regarding the issue.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 28,
                "text": "Jason Collins"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 32,
                "end": 53,
                "text": "+1-607-527-2095x58489"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 28,
                "text": "Jason Collins"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 32,
                "end": 53,
                "text": "+1-607-527-2095x58489"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Edward Lane's SSN is 201-73-3302 and works in New Bonnie.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "text": "Edward Lane"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 56,
                "text": "New Bonnie"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 21,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "201-73-3302"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "text": "Edward Lane's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 21,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "201-73-3302"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 56,
                "text": "New Bonnie"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 168.22.134.120 was accessed by Ronald Graham.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 63,
                "text": "Ronald Graham"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "168.22.134.120"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "168.22.134.120"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 63,
                "text": "Ronald Graham"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "168.22.134.120"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Scott Cooper booked flight tickets on 2025-07-23 and paid using card 4960795370552627173.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "text": "Scott Cooper"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 38,
                "end": 48,
                "text": "2025-07-23"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 88,
                "text": "4960795370552627173"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "text": "Scott Cooper"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 38,
                "end": 48,
                "text": "2025-07-23"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Robert Richardson booked flight tickets on 1981-07-08 and paid using card 2711375080296413.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 17,
                "text": "Robert Richardson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 43,
                "end": 53,
                "text": "1981-07-08"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 74,
                "end": 90,
                "text": "2711375080296413"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 17,
                "text": "Robert Richardson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 43,
                "end": 53,
                "text": "1981-07-08"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_BANK_NUMBER",
                "start": 74,
                "end": 90,
                "text": "2711375080296413"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 74,
                "end": 90,
                "text": "2711375080296413"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Visit http://www.ewing.com/ for more information or email davisbrian@example.org.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 58,
                "end": 80,
                "text": "davisbrian@example.org"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 27,
                "text": "http://www.ewing.com/"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 58,
                "end": 80,
                "text": "davisbrian@example.org"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 27,
                "text": "http://www.ewing.com/"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 80,
                "text": "example.org"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Visit http://www.hill-davidson.net/ for more information or email ewalsh@example.org.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 66,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "ewalsh@example.org"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 35,
                "text": "http://www.hill-davidson.net/"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 66,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "ewalsh@example.org"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 35,
                "text": "http://www.hill-davidson.net/"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "example.org"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Driver license RKB-184 belongs to David Duncan who resides in South Dawntown.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 46,
                "text": "David Duncan"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 62,
                "end": 76,
                "text": "South Dawntown"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "RKB-184"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 46,
                "text": "David Duncan"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 62,
                "end": 76,
                "text": "South Dawntown"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 223.229.85.25 was accessed by Derek Robinson.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 63,
                "text": "Derek Robinson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "223.229.85.25"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "223.229.85.25"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 63,
                "text": "Derek Robinson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "text": "223.229.85.25"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "April Brown booked flight tickets on 1981-04-18 and paid using card 3581806074600918.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "text": "April Brown"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "1981-04-18"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 68,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "3581806074600918"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 68,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "3581806074600918"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "text": "April Brown"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "1981-04-18"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_BANK_NUMBER",
                "start": 68,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "3581806074600918"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 68,
                "end": 84,
                "text": "3581806074600918"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Please contact Andre Cole on 272-523-6661x07960 regarding the issue.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "Andre Cole"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 29,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "272-523-6661x07960"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "Andre Cole"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 29,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "272-523-6661x07960"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Jennifer Craig's SSN is 756-13-9061 and works in Shepherdville.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 14,
                "text": "Jennifer Craig"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 62,
                "text": "Shepherdville"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 24,
                "end": 35,
                "text": "756-13-9061"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "text": "Jennifer Craig's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 24,
                "end": 35,
                "text": "756-13-9061"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 49,
                "end": 62,
                "text": "Shepherdville"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 173.201.83.233 was accessed by Raymond Payne Jr..",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 67,
                "text": "Raymond Payne Jr."
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "173.201.83.233"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "173.201.83.233"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 66,
                "text": "Raymond Payne Jr"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 1
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Ana Smith's SSN is 249-31-6935 and works in Samanthastad.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "text": "Ana Smith"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 44,
                "end": 56,
                "text": "Samanthastad"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "249-31-6935"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "text": "Ana Smith's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "249-31-6935"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 44,
                "end": 56,
                "text": "Samanthastad"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Driver license 681X9 belongs to Jacob Kirby who resides in Leeton.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 32,
                "end": 43,
                "text": "Jacob Kirby"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 59,
                "end": 65,
                "text": "Leeton"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 20,
                "text": "681X9"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 32,
                "end": 43,
                "text": "Jacob Kirby"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 59,
                "end": 65,
                "text": "Leeton"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is John Frost and I live in West Melissaberg. You can reach me at bellis@example.com.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 21,
                "text": "John Frost"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 36,
                "end": 52,
                "text": "West Melissaberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 74,
                "end": 92,
                "text": "bellis@example.com"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 74,
                "end": 92,
                "text": "bellis@example.com"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 21,
                "text": "John Frost"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 36,
                "end": 52,
                "text": "West Melissaberg"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 81,
                "end": 92,
                "text": "example.com"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 6.9.212.1 was accessed by Robert Russo.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 45,
                "end": 57,
                "text": "Robert Russo"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 28,
                "text": "6.9.212.1"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 28,
                "text": "6.9.212.1"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 45,
                "end": 57,
                "text": "Robert Russo"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Jennifer Hammond booked flight tickets on 1978-10-26 and paid using card 676321852367.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "text": "Jennifer Hammond"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 42,
                "end": 52,
                "text": "1978-10-26"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "CREDIT_CARD",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "676321852367"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "text": "Jennifer Hammond"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 42,
                "end": 52,
                "text": "1978-10-26"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_BANK_NUMBER",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "676321852367"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 73,
                "end": 85,
                "text": "676321852367"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Passport number P35651822 is registered under Eric Brown.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 56,
                "text": "Eric Brown"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P35651822"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 56,
                "text": "Eric Brown"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P35651822"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P35651822"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Visit http://palmer.com/ for more information or email lvaughan@example.net.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 55,
                "end": 75,
                "text": "lvaughan@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 24,
                "text": "http://palmer.com/"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 55,
                "end": 75,
                "text": "lvaughan@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 6,
                "end": 24,
                "text": "http://palmer.com/"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 64,
                "end": 75,
                "text": "example.net"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "John Shaw's SSN is 896-26-6061 and works in Milesview.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "text": "John Shaw"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 44,
                "end": 53,
                "text": "Milesview"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "896-26-6061"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "text": "John Shaw's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "896-26-6061"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 44,
                "end": 53,
                "text": "Milesview"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 1
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Passport number P39072275 is registered under Craig Miller.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 58,
                "text": "Craig Miller"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P39072275"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 58,
                "text": "Craig Miller"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P39072275"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P39072275"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Allen Ellison's SSN is 372-80-6485 and works in Lindseyside.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "text": "Allen Ellison"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 48,
                "end": 59,
                "text": "Lindseyside"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 23,
                "end": 34,
                "text": "372-80-6485"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "text": "Allen Ellison's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 23,
                "end": 34,
                "text": "372-80-6485"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 1
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Stephanie Davenport and I live in Whitestad. You can reach me at monicafisher@example.com.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "Stephanie Davenport"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 45,
                "end": 54,
                "text": "Whitestad"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 76,
                "end": 100,
                "text": "monicafisher@example.com"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 76,
                "end": 100,
                "text": "monicafisher@example.com"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "Stephanie Davenport"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 45,
                "end": 54,
                "text": "Whitestad"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 89,
                "end": 100,
                "text": "example.com"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 2,
        "fn": 1,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Mary Mckee's SSN is 653-51-1096 and works in East Briana.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "text": "Mary Mckee"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 45,
                "end": 56,
                "text": "East Briana"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 20,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "653-51-1096"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "text": "Mary Mckee's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 20,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "653-51-1096"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 45,
                "end": 56,
                "text": "East Briana"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 95.203.195.180 was accessed by Tina Berry.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 60,
                "text": "Tina Berry"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "95.203.195.180"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 33,
                "text": "95.203.195.180"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 50,
                "end": 60,
                "text": "Tina Berry"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Please contact Jennifer Hanson on 001-701-361-7452 regarding the issue.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "Jennifer Hanson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 50,
                "text": "001-701-361-7452"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 15,
                "end": 30,
                "text": "Jennifer Hanson"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PHONE_NUMBER",
                "start": 34,
                "end": 50,
                "text": "001-701-361-7452"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Passport number P68933100 is registered under Ashley Williams.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "Ashley Williams"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P68933100"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 46,
                "end": 61,
                "text": "Ashley Williams"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_PASSPORT",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P68933100"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_DRIVER_LICENSE",
                "start": 16,
                "end": 25,
                "text": "P68933100"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "My name is Crystal Kim and I live in North John. You can reach me at goldensean@example.net.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "Crystal Kim"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "North John"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 91,
                "text": "goldensean@example.net"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "EMAIL_ADDRESS",
                "start": 69,
                "end": 91,
                "text": "goldensean@example.net"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 11,
                "end": 22,
                "text": "Crystal Kim"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "text": "North John"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "URL",
                "start": 80,
                "end": 91,
                "text": "example.net"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 3
    },
    {
        "input_text": "Tony Carey's SSN is 136-79-2528 and works in South Michael.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "text": "Tony Carey"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 45,
                "end": 58,
                "text": "South Michael"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 20,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "136-79-2528"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "text": "Tony Carey's"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "US_SSN",
                "start": 20,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "136-79-2528"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "LOCATION",
                "start": 45,
                "end": 58,
                "text": "South Michael"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 3,
        "fp": 0,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
        "input_text": "The server with IP 182.30.0.113 was accessed by Veronica Brown.",
        "expected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 48,
                "end": 62,
                "text": "Veronica Brown"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "182.30.0.113"
            }
        ],
        "detected": [
            {
                "entity_type": "IP_ADDRESS",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "182.30.0.113"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "DATE_TIME",
                "start": 19,
                "end": 31,
                "text": "182.30.0.113"
            },
            {
                "entity_type": "PERSON",
                "start": 48,
                "end": 62,
                "text": "Veronica Brown"
            }
        ],
        "tp": 2,
        "fp": 1,
        "fn": 0,
        "exact_match": 2
    },
    {
